To guide coding agents in making
informed decisions and accurately using
open- source libraries at the correct
versions, we need to provide the agents
with the necessary contextual
information about the libraries they're
coding against.
We're starting from within Claude Code.
We want to build a new MCP server and I
know I want to use fast MCP. So I start
by asking Claude Code to search for the
latest usage spec for fast MCP.
It searches the Tessle spec registry
using the Tessle MCP server we connected
earlier. We found a usage spec at
version 2122 for fastmcp. So, we'll go
ahead and install it onto our machine.
This will download it onto my file
system for my agent to use.
Let's go back to the file system and
take a look at the usage specs we
downloaded for fast MCP. Tessle spec
registry will hold one or more usage
specs per library. In this case, we have
10. Let's take a look at the
authentication usage spec that
describing the APIs and intended usage.
This information is vital for our agent
to code effectively using fast MCP.
I've now given my agent the knowledge
and context it needs to code effectively
with open-source libraries using
Tessle's usage specs.